[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "I should be asking you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "should", "be", "asking", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, she does.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I don't think people are rushing up to you on the streets of America saying legalize heroin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "people", "are", "rushing", "up", "to", "you", "on", "the", "streets", "of", "America", "saying", "legalize", "heroin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "That's common sense, are they?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "common", "sense", ",", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "That's not supporting choice, it is?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "supporting", "choice", ",", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I think you're mixed up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "mixed", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "What would you hope to gain from this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "hope", "to", "gain", "from", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "I can't hammer nails for the rest of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "hammer", "nails", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "When you have seen what's happened to America, and you have seen the emergence of the Tea Party as a proper formidable political force, do you feel a slight twinge of regret that you're not at the forefront of this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "have", "seen", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "America", ",", "and", "you", "have", "seen", "the", "emergence", "of", "the", "Tea", "Party", "as", "a", "proper", "formidable", "political", "force", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "a", "slight", "twinge", "of", "regret", "that", "you", "'re", "not", "at", "the", "forefront", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "You know, I don't think that there's a lot to be gained from the might-have-beens, to the would-have-beens, to the could-have- beens of life.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "to", "be", "gained", "from", "the", "might-have-beens", ",", "to", "the", "would-have-beens", ",", "to", "the", "could-have-", "beens", "of", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "But do you agree then with Warren Buffett when he said today that the tax system has to be reformed to hammer people like him more, the super rich who are paying a disproportionate amount of tax and their total tax rates compared to the guy on the street?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "agree", "then", "with", "Warren", "Buffett", "when", "he", "said", "today", "that", "the", "tax", "system", "has", "to", "be", "reformed", "to", "hammer", "people", "like", "him", "more", ",", "the", "super", "rich", "who", "are", "paying", "a", "disproportionate", "amount", "of", "tax", "and", "their", "total", "tax", "rates", "compared", "to", "the", "guy", "on", "the", "street", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I would say I absolutely believe in the notion of tax reform.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "I", "absolutely", "believe", "in", "the", "notion", "of", "tax", "reform", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Who do you think fundamentally has what it takes in the overall package to seriously challenge Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "fundamentally", "has", "what", "it", "takes", "in", "the", "overall", "package", "to", "seriously", "challenge", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I think that the primary system will winnow that out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "the", "primary", "system", "will", "winnow", "that", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "ANFORD: Well, you know, you're trying to get me to pick a horse and I don't want to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["ANFORD", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "'re", "trying", "to", "get", "me", "to", "pick", "a", "horse", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Do you think he is persuadable as we get through the next few months and we're heading towards the first proper primary, could you see him rallying to the cause of the party if no one has emerged by then that people don't think could beat Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "is", "persuadable", "as", "we", "get", "through", "the", "next", "few", "months", "and", "we", "'re", "heading", "towards", "the", "first", "proper", "primary", ",", "could", "you", "see", "him", "rallying", "to", "the", "cause", "of", "the", "party", "if", "no", "one", "has", "emerged", "by", "then", "that", "people", "do", "n't", "think", "could", "beat", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Well, I think that there's talk of that still happening.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "talk", "of", "that", "still", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Presumably, you would lean more towards a Tea Party nominee than you would towards one of the more moderate type like a Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Presumably", ",", "you", "would", "lean", "more", "towards", "a", "Tea", "Party", "nominee", "than", "you", "would", "towards", "one", "of", "the", "more", "moderate", "type", "like", "a", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "NNS", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "NNS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Is she the obvious person now beginning to capture enough of the public's imagination to potentially be that person?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "the", "obvious", "person", "now", "beginning", "to", "capture", "enough", "of", "the", "public", "'s", "imagination", "to", "potentially", "be", "that", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "But of those names, of the three, you know, which one if you had to put one in the race tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["But", "of", "those", "names", ",", "of", "the", "three", ",", "you", "know", ",", "which", "one", "if", "you", "had", "to", "put", "one", "in", "the", "race", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I'm not going to pick a horse.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "pick", "a", "horse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "How does that feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "It's humbling.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "humbling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Given that, do you feel great regret, or is that the wrong emotion to put to you?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "that", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "great", "regret", ",", "or", "is", "that", "the", "wrong", "emotion", "to", "put", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, I think that -- I mean, anybody who has been married doesn't start at the beginning thinking boy, I hope I some day get divorced.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "anybody", "who", "has", "been", "married", "does", "n't", "start", "at", "the", "beginning", "thinking", "boy", ",", "I", "hope", "I", "some", "day", "get", "divorced", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What do you think you have learned about yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "learned", "about", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I think learned a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "learned", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "How has the public been with you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "the", "public", "been", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "They're incredible.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "incredible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "It was fabulous.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "fabulous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What would you do differently?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "differently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "A whole host of things, none of which are particularly productive in terms of my boys, who might be watching this show.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "whole", "host", "of", "things", ",", "none", "of", "which", "are", "particularly", "productive", "in", "terms", "of", "my", "boys", ",", "who", "might", "be", "watching", "this", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Would anything have really made much difference?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "anything", "have", "really", "made", "much", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Having got it wrong in your marriage, do you feel like you have learned enough from that whole experience, and the bruising exposure and scandal to get it right now?", "question_tokens": ["Having", "got", "it", "wrong", "in", "your", "marriage", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "have", "learned", "enough", "from", "that", "whole", "experience", ",", "and", "the", "bruising", "exposure", "and", "scandal", "to", "get", "it", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I would hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Are you happier in yourself now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happier", "in", "yourself", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "How would you describe the experience?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "the", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Fabulous.", "answer_tokens": ["Fabulous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What are you thinking when you're there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "thinking", "when", "you", "'re", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I think that there is a tremendous value to the valleys of life, that the football team that loses on Friday night probably thinks a whole lot more of what they might get right or what they might do differently than the team that won.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "there", "is", "a", "tremendous", "value", "to", "the", "valleys", "of", "life", ",", "that", "the", "football", "team", "that", "loses", "on", "Friday", "night", "probably", "thinks", "a", "whole", "lot", "more", "of", "what", "they", "might", "get", "right", "or", "what", "they", "might", "do", "differently", "than", "the", "team", "that", "won", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Have you, in an odd way, had more time now to develop a better relationship with your sons than you may have done if you continued in the ever more punishing political world?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", ",", "in", "an", "odd", "way", ",", "had", "more", "time", "now", "to", "develop", "a", "better", "relationship", "with", "your", "sons", "than", "you", "may", "have", "done", "if", "you", "continued", "in", "the", "ever", "more", "punishing", "political", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "They say so.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "say", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Who of your family have been the real rocks of support outside of your sons?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "of", "your", "family", "have", "been", "the", "real", "rocks", "of", "support", "outside", "of", "your", "sons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I've redeveloped a really neat relationship with my sister.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "redeveloped", "a", "really", "neat", "relationship", "with", "my", "sister", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I mean, the obvious in terms of I'm disappointed and here is why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "obvious", "in", "terms", "of", "I", "'m", "disappointed", "and", "here", "is", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Which is a pretty powerful endorsement to have, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "a", "pretty", "powerful", "endorsement", "to", "have", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Important one.", "answer_tokens": ["Important", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "You must be tempted, aren't you, to have another go at this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "tempted", ",", "are", "n't", "you", ",", "to", "have", "another", "go", "at", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "If you had the power, what is the one thing you would do to dramatically reform the tax system, which would make a real difference in reducing America's debt?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "the", "power", ",", "what", "is", "the", "one", "thing", "you", "would", "do", "to", "dramatically", "reform", "the", "tax", "system", ",", "which", "would", "make", "a", "real", "difference", "in", "reducing", "America", "'s", "debt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I don't think it's a question of the tax system.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "question", "of", "the", "tax", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "It can't just be cutting spending, can it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "ca", "n't", "just", "be", "cutting", "spending", ",", "can", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "At some stage, you have to bring in more revenues as well, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["At", "some", "stage", ",", "you", "have", "to", "bring", "in", "more", "revenues", "as", "well", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, I would argue no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "argue", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "It's true.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Do you have any plans to remarry?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "plans", "to", "remarry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "We'll see.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "That's not a denial, Mr. Governor?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "a", "denial", ",", "Mr.", "Governor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Nor is it an answer.", "answer_tokens": ["Nor", "is", "it", "an", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Governor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Would it be a nice ending to the saga for you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "be", "a", "nice", "ending", "to", "the", "saga", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 613, "question": "You have, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "No, you're going into -- again that personal sphere that out of respect for my boys --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "'re", "going", "into", "--", "again", "that", "personal", "sphere", "that", "out", "of", "respect", "for", "my", "boys", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]